Guide to the Department of Germanic Languages, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1929-1989; Accession 1990-A-122
  - Correspondence, 1968 September - 1972 August
    - 1.6 Monatshefte/other Journal Entries, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 370)
    - 2.4 Graduate Reading Course, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 371)
    - 2.5 Summer Language Institute, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 372)
    - 2.10 Film Course, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 373)
    - 3.1 Cocktail Party, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 374)
    - 3.2 Lecturers and Visitors, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 375)
    - 3.3 Woodward Lectures Record, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 376)
    - 3.4 Film Showings/Fernsehspiele, undated (Box 5, Folder 377)
    - 3.5 Special Events, current year, 1979-1984 (Box 5, Folder 378)
    - 4.0 General Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 379)
    - 4.1 Job Applications, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 380)
    - 4.2 Vacancies - Elsewhere, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 381)
    - V.1.2 Beinecke Rare Book Library, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 382)
    - 1.5 Sterling Memorial Library, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 383)
    - 2.1 German, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 384)
    - 2.1.8 DDR -Embassy, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 385)
    - 2.2 Austrian/Austrian Institute, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 386)
    - 3.1 AATG/AAUP, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 387)
    - 3.2 Goethe House, NY and Goethe Institute, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 388)
    - 3.3 Modern Language Association, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 389)
    - 3.4 Northeastern Conference, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 390)
    - 4.0 Lothar Hausmann Memorial Fund, 1976-1981 (Box 6, Folder 391)
    - 4.1 Fellowships and Lectureships, general andPrizes, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 392)
    - 4.1.1 Morse Fellowships, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 393)
    - 4.1.3 Fulbright Fellowships/NEH, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 394)
    - 4.2 Scott Prize, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 395)
    - 4.3 Book Prize (lacking), undated (Box 6, Folder 396)
    - 4.6 Moore Fund, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 397)
    - 5.1 DAAD, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 398)
    - 5.2 Leavenworth Professorship, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 399)
    - Office of Foreign Students/Scholars' Information, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 400)
    - Broch Symposium, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 401)
    - Literature Committee, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 402)
    - 111.1.2 Communication Department, 1975-1985 (Box 6, Folder 403)
    - 1.3 Yale Faculty Club, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 404)
    - 1.4 Office Machines Maintenance Contracts, 1979-1985 (Box 6, Folder 405)
    - 2.0 Office of the Council of Masters, 1978-1984 (Box 6, Folder 406)
    - 2.1 Dean Yale College/Dean Graduate School, 1976-1984 (Box 6, Folder 407)
    - 2.2 Secretary's Office, 1976-1984 (Box 6, Folder 408)
    - 2.3 Office of Facilities Planning, 1975-1985 (Box 6, Folder 409)
    - 2.5 Computer Center, 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 410)
    - 2.6 Language Lab. A-V Center, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 411)
    - 2.7 Office of the Foreign Student Advisor, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 412)
    - 2.9 Committee, Council andDivision of the Humanities, 1978-1983 (Box 6, Folder 413)
    - 2.10 Comptroller's Office/Treasurer's Office, 1976-1984 (Box 6, Folder 414)
    - 2.15 Personnel Office, 1976-1985 (Box 6, Folder 415)
    - 2.16 Kisc. Departments and Committees, 1976-1984 (Box 6, Folder 416)
    - 2.19 Director of Graduate Studies, 1975-1984 (Box 6, Folder 417)
    - 2.19.8 Director of Undergraduate Studies, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 418)
    - 2.20 Concilium on International Studies, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 419)
    - 2.24 University Council, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 420)
    - 2.25 Council for International EXChange of Scholars, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 421)
    - 2.26 Modern Studies Program, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 422)
    - 2.27 Chairmen -Group, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 423)
    - 3.1 Courses - general, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 424)
    - 3.1.8 Women's Studies for Yale College, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 425)
    - 3.2 Course Curricular Discussions, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 426)
    - 3.3 Course of Studies Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 427)
    - 3.4 Yale College, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 428)
    - 3.5 Election and Enrollment Statistics, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 429)
    - 3.6 Grading. general, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 430)
    - 3.8 Faculty Committee on Teaching andLearning, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 431)
    - 3.12 Summer Programs, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 432)
    - 4.3 Bursary Students, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 433)
    - 4.6 Junior Year Abroad, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 434)
    - 4.7 Majors/Literature Majors, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 435)
    - IV.1.3 Circulars, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 436)
    - 1.4 Tutors, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 437)
    - 1.6 MonBtshefte/other Journal Entries, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 438)
    - 1.8 Yale Literary Magazine, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 439)
    - 2.0 Committee on Graduate Instruction in German Literature (lacking), undated (Box 6, Folder 440)
    - 2.5 Summer Language Institute, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 441)
    - 2.7 Language Laboratory, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 442)
    - 2.9 Modern Studies Program, ·1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 443)
    - 3.1 Cocktail Party, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 444)
    - 3.2 Lecturers and Visitors. general, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 445)
    - 3.3 Woodward Lectures Record, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 446)
    - 3.4 Film Showings/Fernsehspiele (Box 6, Folder 447)
    - 3.5 Special Events. Current Year, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 448)
    - 4.0 General Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 449)
    - 4.1 Job Applications, 1976-1985 (Box 7, Folder 450)
    - 4.2 Vacancies Elsewhere, 1977-1985 (Box 7, Folder 451)
    - V.1.l German Seminar Library, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 452)
    - 1.2 Beinecke Rare Book Library, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 453)
    - 1.3 German Reading Section -eeL (lacking), undated (Box 7, Folder 454)
    - 1.4 Teacher's Library (lacking), undated (Box 7, Folder 455)
    - 1.5 Sterling Memorial Library, 1972-1978 (Box 7, Folder 456)
    - 1.6 Broch Archive, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 457)
    - 2.1 German, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 458)
    - 2.2 Austrian, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 459)
    - 2.3 Swiss, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 460)
    - 3.1 AATG/NICL, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 461)
    - 3.2 Goethe House, NY and Goethe Institutes, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 462)
    - 3.3 Modern Language Association, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 463)
    - 3.4 Northeastern Conference, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 464)
    - 3.5 Princeton - ETS (lacking), undated (Box 7, Folder 465)
    - 3.6 Teaching Aid Project (lacking), undated (Box 7, Folder 466)
    - 3.7 ACTFL - American Council for the Teaching of Foreign Languages (lacking), undated (Box 7, Folder 467)
    - 4.0 Lothar Hausmann Memorial Fund (lacking), undated (Box 7, Folder 468)
    - 4.1 Fellowships and Lectureships, general/Prizes, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 469)
    - 4.1.1 Morse Fellowships, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 470)
    - 4.1.2 Junior Faculty Summer Research Support (lacking), undated (Box 7, Folder 471)
    - 4.1.3 Senior Fellowships, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 472)
    - 4.1.4 Fulbright Fellowships, undated (Box 7, Folder 473)
    - 4.2 Scott Prize (lacking), undated (Box 7, Folder 474)
    - 4.3 Book Prizes (lacking), undated (Box 7, Folder 475)
    - 4.4 Yale Funds, undated (Box 7, Folder 476)
    - 4.5 Honorary Degree, undated (Box 7, Folder 477)
    - 4.6 Moore Fund, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 478)
    - 5.1 DAAD, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 479)
    - 5.2 Elias W. Leavenworth Professorship, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 480)
    - 5.3 US Office of Education - Foreign Curriculum Consultant Program, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 481)
    - 5.4 Council for International Exchange of Scholars, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 482)
    - Provost Question, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 483)
    - Dean Search, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 484)
    - III.1.1 Books, 1974-1984 (Box 7, Folder 485)
    - 1.2 Telephone/Postal Service, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 486)
    - 1.3 Alterations, Equipment, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 487)
    - 1.4 Travel Expenses, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 488)
    - 1.5 Yale Faculty Club, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 489)
    - 1.6 Office Machines. Maintenance Contracts, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 490)
    - 2.0 Office of the Council of Masters, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 491)
    - 2.1 Dean Yale College/Dean Graduate School, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 492)
    - 2.2 Secretary's Office, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 493)
    - 2.3 Space Allocation, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 494)
    - 2.5 Computer Center, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 495)
    - 2.9 Committee on Humanities, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 496)
    - 2.9.n National Humanities Institute, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 497)
    - 2.9.8 Humanities Division Project, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 498)
    - 2.10 Comptroller's Office/Treasurer's Office, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 499)
    - 2.12 Yale Travel Office, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 500)
    - 2.14 Safety Policy andSafety Organizations, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 501)
    - 2.15 Personnel Office, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 502)
    - 2.16 Miscellaneous Department andCommittees, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 503)
    - 2.19 Director of Graduate Studies, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 504)
    - 2.20 Concilium on International Studies, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 505)
    - 2.23 Foreign Television Library Center, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 506)
    - 3.0 German 15 (lacking), undated (Box 7, Folder 507)
    - 3.1 Courses. general, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 508)
    - 3.3 Course of Studies Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 509)
    - 3.4 Yale College, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 510)
    - 3.5 Election and Enrollment Statistics, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 511)
    - 3.6 Grading. general, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 512)
    - 3.8 Faculty Committee on Teaching and Learning, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 513)
    - 3.10 Yale Co-op Textbooks, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 514)
    - 3.11 College Seminars, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 515)
    - 3.12 Summer Programs, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 516)
    - 4.3 Bursary Students, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 517)
    - 4.6 Junior Year Abroad, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 518)
    - 4.7 Majors/Literature Majors, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 519)
    - IV.1.3 Circulars, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 520)
    - 1.4 Tutors, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 521)
    - 1.6 Monatshefte/other Journal Entries, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 522)
    - 2.1 Graduate Courses, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 523)
    - 2.3 Scandinavian Course, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 524)
    - 2.5 Summer Language Institute, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 525)
    - 3.1 Cocktail Party, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 526)
    - 3.2 Lecturers and Visitors. general, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 527)
    - 3.3 Woodward Lectures Record, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 528)
    - 3.4 Film Showings/Fernsehspiele, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 529)
    - 3.5 Special Events, Current, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 530)
    - 4.0 General Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 531)
    - 4.1 Job Applications, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 532)
    - 4.2 Vacancies Elsewhere, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 533)
    - 4.3 Graduate Schools Elsewhere, undated (Box 7, Folder 534)
    - 4.4 Summerschools Elsewhere, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 535)
    - V.1.0 Books. Gifts, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 536)
    - 1.5 Sterling Memorial Library, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 537)
    - 2.1 German/Goethe Institute, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 538)
    - 2.2 Austrian, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 539)
    - 3. 1 AATG, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 540)
    - 3.2 Goethe Society and Goethe House, NY, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 541)
    - 3.3 Modern Language Association, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 542)
    - 3.4 Northeast Conference, undated (Box 7, Folder 543)
    - 4.1 Fellowships andLectureships. general, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 544)
    - 4.1.1 Morse Fellowships (Box 7, Folder 545)
    - 4.3 Book Prizes, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 546)
    - 5.1 DAAD, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 547)
    - Faust -Gesellschaft, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 548)
    - NEMLA Project, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 549)
    - Language Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 550)
    - 111.1.1 Books (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 551)
    - 1.2 Telephone, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 552)
    - 1.3 Alterations/Equipment, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 553)
    - 1.4 Travel Expenses (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 554)
    - 1.5 Yale Faculty Club (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 555)
    - 1.6 Office Machines Maintenance Contracts, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 556)
    - 2.0 Office of the Council of Masters (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 557)
    - 2.1 Dean Yale College/Dean Graduate School, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 558)
    - 2.2 Secretary's Office, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 559)
    - 2.3 Space Allocation, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 560)
    - 2.4 Housing Bureau (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 561)
    - 2.5 Computer Center, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 562)
    - 2.6 Language Lab/Audiovisual Center, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 563)
    - 2.7 Office of the Foreign Student Advisor, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 564)
    - 2.8 Yale University Council, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 565)
    - 2.9 Committee on Humanities, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 566)
    - 2.10 Comptroller's Office/Treasurer's Office, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 567)
    - 2.11 Yale Art Gallery (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 568)
    - 2.12 Yale Travel Office (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 569)
    - 2.13 Office of Educational Research (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 570)
    - 2.14 Safety Policy and Safety Organizations (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 571)
    - 2.15 Personnel Office, 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 572)
    - 2.16 Miscellaneous Departments andCommittees, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 573)
    - 2.17 Yale Literature Group (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 574)
    - 2.18 Faculty Research Grant, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 575)
    - 2.19 Director of Graduate Studies, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 576)
    - 2.20 Concilium on International Studies, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 577)
    - 2.21 Language Cocmittee, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 578)
    - 2.22 Coeducation, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 579)
    - 3.0 German 15 (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 580)
    - 3.1 Courses, general, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 581)
    - 3.2 Course Curricular Discussions (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 582)
    - 3.3 Course of Studies Committee, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 583)
    - 3.4 Yale College, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 584)
    - 3.5 Election and Enrollment Statistics, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 585)
    - 3.6 Grading, general, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 586)
    - 3.7 Students Committee on Teaching, SAB (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 587)
    - 3.8 Faculty Committee on Teaching andLearning, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 588)
    - 3.9 Grievance Committee (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 589)
    - 3.10 Yale Co-op Textbooks, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 590)
    - 3.11 College Seminars, undated (Box 8, Folder 591)
    - 3.12 Summer Progrnms in 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 592)
    - 4.1 Teaching Assignments (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 593)
    - 4.2 White Pamphlet (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 594)
    - 4.3 Bursary Students, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 595)
    - 4.4 Departmental Examinations and Proctoring (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 596)
    - 4.5 Advanced Placement (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - 4.6 Junior Year Abroad (Box 8, Folder 598)
    - 4.7 Majors/Literature Majors, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 599)
    - 4.8 Special Majors (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 600)
    - 4.9 Coeducation, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 601)
    - IV.1.1 Directories. rosters, undated (Box 8, Folder 602)
    - 1.2 Faculty Offices (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 603)
    - 1.3 Circulars, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 604)
    - 1.4 Tutors, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 605)
    - 1.5 Departmental Consultant and Placement Officers (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 606)
    - 1.6 Monatahefte/other Journal Entries, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 607)
    - 1.7 Zeitschriften (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 608)
    - 2.0 Committee on Graduate Instruction in German Literature (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 609)
    - 2.1 Graduate Courses, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 610)
    - 2.2 Dutch Course (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 611)
    - 2.3 Scandinavian Course (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 612)
    - 2.4 Graduate Reading Course (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 613)
    - 2.5 Summer Language Institute, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 614)
    - 2.6 Linguistics Department (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 615)
    - 2.7 Language Laboratory, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 616)
    - 2.8 German Studies Program Curriculum, 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 617)
    - 3.1 Cocktail Party, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 618)
    - 3.2 Lecturers and Visitors. general, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 619)
    - 3.3 Woodward Lectures Record, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 620)
    - 3.4 Film Showings, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 621)
    - 3.5 Special Events. current year, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 622)
    - 4.0 General Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 623)
    - 4.1 Job Applications, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 624)
    - 4.1 Job Applications, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 625)
    - 4.2 Vacancies Elsewhere, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 626)
    - 4.3 Graduate Schools Elsewhere (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 627)
    - 4.4 Summerschools Elsewhere (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 628)
    - 4.5 Opportunities Abroad (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 629)
    - V.1.0 Books. Gifts, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 630)
    - 1.1 German Seminar Library (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 631)
    - 1.2 Beinecke Rare Book Library (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 632)
    - 1.3 German Reading Section -CCL (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 633)
    - 1.4 Teacher's Library (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 634)
    - 1.5 Sterling Memorial Library (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 635)
    - 2.1 German Consulate. Goethe Institute, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 636)
    - 2.2 Austrian Consulate/Institute (Box 8, Folder 637)
    - 2.3 Swiss Consulate (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 638)
    - 3.1 AArG (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 639)
    - 3.2 Goethe Institute/Goethe House. NY, undated (Box 8, Folder 640)
    - 3.3 MLA, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 641)
    - 3.4 Northeastern Conference, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 642)
    - 3.5 Princeton -ETS (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 643)
    - 3.6 Teaching Aid Project (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 644)
    - 3.7 ACTFL, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 645)
    - 4.1 Fellowships and Lectureships. general, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 646)
    - 4.1.1 Morse Fellowships, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 647)
    - 4.1.2 Junior Faculty Summer Research Support, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 648)
    - 4.1.3 Senior Fellowships (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 649)
    - 4.1.4 Fulbright Fellowships, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 650)
    - 4.2 Scott Prize, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 651)
    - 4.2 Book Prizes (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 652)
    - 0 (Box 8, Folder system_indicator_f8d1d5dccddcbc959513db632d852eb1)
    - 4.4 Yale Funds (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 653)
    - 4.5 Honorary Degree (lacking), undated (Box 8, Folder 654)
    - 4.6 Moore Fund, undated (Box 8, Folder 655)
    - V. 5.1 DAAD, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 656)
  - Peter Demetz correspondence
    - Correspondence for Professor Demetz, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 657)
  - Old budgets and appointments
    - 1.1 Budget, 1954-1964
      - 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 659)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 660)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 661)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 662)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 663)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 664)
      - 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 665)
      - 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 666)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 667)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 668)
    - 1.1 Budget Matters I, 1929-45 (Box 9, Folder 669)
    - 1.1 Budget Matters II, 1945-1965 (Box 9, Folder 670)
    - 1.1. 2 Budget, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 671)
    - 1.1. 2 Budget, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 672)
    - Secretaries, 1954-1958 (Box 9, Folder 673)
    - 2.3 Appointments
      - (old) 1931-48 (Box 9, Folder 674)
      - 1954-1957 (Box 9, Folder 675)
    - 2.3 Appointments, 1960-1963 (Box 9, Folder 676)
    - Contributions to Indiana University, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 677)
    - 1.3.1 Correspondence with President, 1968-1984 (Box 9, Folder 678)
    - 3.2 Correspondence with Provost, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 679)
    - 11.1.2 Regulations: Leave of Absence, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 680)
    - 2.1 Vacancies at Yale (candidates), 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 681)
    - 2.2 Appoinment Summaries, 1968-1983 (Box 9, Folder 682)
    - 3.2 Teaching Assistants and Associates, 1968-1972 (Box 9, Folder 683)
    - 3.4 PhD Candidates, 1968-1972 (Box 9, Folder 684)
  - Student course evaluations
    - Course Evaluation Forms, Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 695-19697)
    - Course Impnavement Forms -German 130, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 701)
    - Affirmative Action Program, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 707)
    - Correspondence re: Lorna Martens. The Diary Novel, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 708)
  - Pre-1968 records
    - I.1.1 Budget, general, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 709)
    - 1.2 Budget, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 710)
    - 1.2 Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 711)
    - 1.3 Needs for the future, 1958-1963 (Box 10, Folder 712)
    - 2.0 Germanic Languages, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 713)
    - 3.1 Confidential Correspondence with the President, 1963-1968 (Box 10, Folder 714)
    - 3.2 Confidential Correspondence with the Provost, 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 715)
    - 3.3 Confidential Correspondence with the Faculty, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 716)
    - 3.4 Departmental Minutes, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 717)
    - 3.5 Coneilium on International Studies, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 718)
    - II. 1. 1 Regulations concerning Faculty, general, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 719)
    - 1.1 Regulations governing Faculty, 1962-1966 (Box 10, Folder 720)
    - 1.3 Regulations, TIAA (pension plans), 1958-1967 (Box 10, Folder 721)
    - 1.4 Departmental Policies, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 722)
    - 2.1 Vacancies at Yale (potential job candidates), 1964-1967 (Box 10, Folder 723)
    - 2.1 Applications, 1963-1968
      - 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 724)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 725)
      - 1865-1966 (Box 10, Folder 726)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 727)
    - 2.2 Appointment Summaries, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 728)
    - 2.3 Postdoctoral Fellows, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 729)
    - 2.4 Parttime Employment (tapes, readers. extra clerical help), 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 730)
    - 2.4 Parttime Employment (tapes, readers. extra clerical help, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 731)
    - 2.5 Vacancies at Yale, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 732)
    - 3.1 Graduate Students. general, 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 733)
    - 3.2 Teaching Assistants and Associates, 1965-1957 (Box 10, Folder 734)
    - 3.3 Dissertation Prospectus, general, 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 735)
    - 3.4 PhD Candidates, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 736)
    - 4.1 Applications -Faculty (declined), 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 737)
    - 4.2 Applications -Native Speakers, 1963-1968 (Box 10, Folder 738)
    - 4.3 Applications -Staff, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 739)
    - 5.1 Vacancies Elsewhere (recommendations), 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 740)
    - 5.2 Teacher Placement, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 741)
    - MHG Specialists Survey, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 742)
  - Current administrative and correspondence
    - 1.1 Bursary Boys/old and current, 1966-1971 (Box 10, Folder 757)
    - 1.2 Tentative Teaching Plans, 1966-1971 (Box 10, Folder 758)
    - 1.3 Tentative Teaching Plans, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 759)
    - 1.3 Teaching Assignments, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 760)
    - 1.3 Teaching Assignments, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 761)
    - 1.3.b Tentative Teaching Plans, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 762)
    - 1.4 Special Duties, 1968-1972 (Box 11, Folder 763)
    - 1.5 Enrollment and Election Figures, 1966-1977 (Box 11, Folder 764)
    - 1.5 Department Offerings/Enrollment Figures. etc., 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 765)
    - 1.5 Department Statistics (computer), 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 766)
    - 1.6 Current Enrollment/Election Figures, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 767)
    - 1.7 Offices (Box 11, Folder 768)
    - 1.7 Offices/telephones/classrooms, 1962-1971 (Box 11, Folder 769)